https://bellefrance.com/privacy-policy/

Skip to main contentHomeAbout Belle FranceProtecting your dataPrivacy Policy - Protecting your dataBelle France is a trading name of Alan Rogers Travel Limited (We, Our). We have developed this data protection statement & privacy policy as the privacy and security of your personal information is important to us, and we understand it is important to you.Our data protection statement (summary) and (full) privacy policy explain what personal information we will collect from you and how it will be used. If you do not agree with the details contained within the data protection statement and privacy policy please do not continue to use this website.
Download our (summary) DATA PROTECTION STATEMENT (76.816 KB)
Download our (full) PRIVACY POLICY (124.458 KB)
If you do not have it already, you will need to download and install PDF viewing software of your choice in order to view the PDF files on this site. To download and install Adobe Reader visit: http://get.adobe.com/reader/The authenticFrench holiday specialistFind your holiday todayAll HolidaysPrestige HolidaysGourmet HolidaysWalking HolidaysCycling HolidaysSlower PacedinFranceAlsaceAquitaineArdennesAuvergneBrittanyBurgundyChampagneCharenteCorsicaDordogneFranche-ComtéLanguedoc-RoussillonLimousinLoireLorraineNormandyParisPas de CalaisPays BasquePays de la LoirePicardyProvencePyreneesRhône-AlpesCévennesSpainSearchxWalking & Cycling Holidays in FranceXSearchShow meAll HolidaysArt & CultureGourmetPrestigeSlow PaceTrekeBikes availableTravel by TrainMade for FamiliesGPS on DemandinFranceAlsaceAquitaineArdennesAuvergneBrittanyBurgundyChampagneCharenteCorsicaDordogneFranche-ComtéLanguedoc-RoussillonLimousinLoireLorraineNormandyParisPas de CalaisPays BasquePays de la LoirePicardyProvencePyreneesRhône-AlpesCévennesSpainwithSearchWalking and Cycling Holidays in FranceWalking HolidaysPopular Walking RegionsLoire ValleyProvenceDordogneAlsacePyrénéesPrestige Walking HolidaysGourmet Walking HolidaysSlower Paced Walking HolidaysWalking Holidays By GradeCycling HolidaysPopular Cycling RegionsLoire ValleyDordogneBurgundyCharenteAlsacePrestige Cycling HolidaysGourmet Cycling HolidaysHolidays by eBikeSlower Paced Cycling HolidaysCycling Holidays by GradeLa VelodysseeDestinationsNorthern FranceSouthern FranceCentral FranceEastern FranceWestern FrancePopular RegionsAlsaceAquitaineBrittanyBurgundyCharenteDordogneLoireProvenceWhy Belle FranceAbout Belle FranceContact UsHand Crafted Holidays
Customer Reviews
Travel AdvicePost-Booking InformationPrestige HolidaysHotelsOur BikesMaps, GPS & Route NotesGroup TravelABTA BondedQuick LinksContact UsBlogAbout Belle FranceABTA BondedTravel AdviceTerms & ConditionsPricingPrivacy PolicyBrowser CookiesSitemap
